[dramatic music playing]
[gun cocks]
Look. I don't want to. but...
it's just so much money.
[woman] Money?
Come on. Corrigan. you don't honestly
think you'll get away with this.
[chuckles] Oh. sure I will.
[gunshot]
[gunshots continue]
[woman] Barb.
[yelling] Barb!
-You okay?
-I'm fine. Renee.
Just... distracted.
-Are you sure that there's nothin'...
-I'm fine!
[gunshots continue]
[dramatic music continues]
[theme music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[moody music playing]
You seem a little... tense.
The guy who tried to murder me
is about to walk out of jail.
So. sure. Just a little.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to snap at you.
What's this experiment he volunteered for
all about anyway?
I'll find out tonight at Blackgate.
Barb. you're under no obligation
to be there.
I have to.
Jim Corrigan betrayed me. Renee.
I have to look that animal
in the eyes and...
And... you won't do it alone.
[dramatic music playing]
[gate unlocks. opens]
-[prison guard] Ready. Corrigan?
-No.
But let's do it.
Who'd ya rat out to get
special treatment. Corrigan?
-Miserable son of a--
-Shut up!
[dramatic music continues]
[doors creak open]
[grunts] Hey. hey! Take it easy. fellas.
Good evening. ladies.
What are you doing here. Wayne?
My people told me Dr. Peterson's
longevity experiments
might be worth investing in.
It's all about the money with you.
isn't it?
What else is there?
Well. aside from wine. women.
and the occasional song?
Ladies.
[both] I can't stand him.
I'm Doctor James Peterson.
Head of the Osiris Project.
Tonight. my friends. we stand
at the gateway to a new age.
where the recently deceased
may be resurrected.
And their lives extended by decades.
And we thank Mr. Corrigan for volunteering
to be our first test subject.
[scoffs] For volunteering
to have his sentence reduced.
[machine beeping steadily]
First. we must stop
the test subject's heart.
[groaning]
[suspenseful music playing]
[beeping continues]
[gasps. exhales]
[watch ticking]
[beeping continues]
[suspenseful music continues]
[beeping decreasing]
[sustained beep]
[ticking continues]
[beeping stops]
-[clicking]
-[machine whirring]
[buzzing]
[dramatic music playing]
[whirring intensifies]
[electricity charging up]
[beeping]
[pained screaming]
-[beeping increasing]
-[electrical shocks]
[screaming continues]
[screaming intensifies]
[electricity powers down]
[music intensifies]
He's dead?
Corrigan's dead! He's dead!
If they'll kill a cop.
they'll kill any of us!
We're just lab animals to 'em!
-[prisoners yelling]
-[gasping]
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[grunting]
[yelling continues]
[gasps]
[alarm ringing]
[all] Hmm?
Ladies.
[gasps]
If it's a prison break.
I gotta get you outta here.
I can take care of myself.
Yeah. maybe.
But if those prisoners find out
the police commissioner's daughter's
in here... Let's go.
[suspenseful music continues]
[alarm blaring]
Let me go! Please!
I've got a wife and kids!
Not such a tough guy anymore. huh?
[blaring continues]
[dramatic music playing]
[gate buzzing]
[music intensifying]
[yells. grunts]
[grunts]
[groans]
[fighting grunts and groans]
[dramatic music continues]
[pained yells]
[groans]
-[moody music playing]
-[car driving]
Hell of a way to die...
and it's almost Christmas.
Hate to feel sorry for a guy
like Corrigan. but...
[driver] Yeah. nobody should have
to go out like that.
[suspenseful music playing]
[man] So what are you doin'
for New Year's?
[driver sighs]
Anything like last New Year's.
I'll be trying to walk off
a wicked hangover from--
[both gasp]
-[shrieks]
-[tires screeching]
[screaming]
[crashes]
[dramatic music playing]
[Alfred] Perhaps it's a blessing
the experiment failed.
We're not the most...
responsible species.
And the power to extend
a lifespan indefinitely?
Who decides how to use that? Who's--
But think what a man could accomplish
if he had the time.
-[Alfred] Sir?
-Nothing.
In the spirit of the season. sir.
I was thinking of baking the holiday
biscuits you so enjoyed as a boy.
I remember how you
and your mother would--
[dramatic music continues]
[music sting]
-[brakes screech]
-Ooh. Excuse the jolt. sir.
It appears there's been an accident.
[tense music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[Gordon] You shouldn't have been there
in the first place.
[Barbara] I had to face him. Dad.
-You could've been killed.
-But I wasn't. was I?
I've. uh... got some paperwork
to take care of.
You do that.
[sighs] Thank you. Renee.
I'm okay. Dad.
But...
He died. Dad.
A man died.
And do you know how I felt?
Relieved. [stumbles]
Maybe even happy.
What does that say about me?
It says you've been through
something traumatic. sweetheart.
It says you're human.
Why doesn't that make me feel any better?
I'm gonna head home. Coming?
I'd love to. but I've still got work
to finish up.
Be careful out there. Barb.
Storm's getting rough.
Oh please. I'm a better driver
than you are.
I'll be careful.
[jazzy music playing]
[man] C'mon. Vinny. wrap it up.
[Vinny] Another.
No. Sorry. pally. I gotta get home to--
[slurring] I said gimme another...
"pally."
All right. all right. Calm down. Stay.
Stay as long as you'd like.
[suspenseful music playing]
[door creaks open]
[music intensifies]
[gasps]
[belabored] Vinny...
DeLeon.
Corrigan? Is that you?
Whaddya want?
Vengeance.
[intense music playing]
[high-pitched ringing]
-[heart pounding]
-[gasping in pain]
[groaning. gasps]
[thuds]
[dramatic music playing]
-You're sure that was his name?
-Oh. yeah. Called him Corrigan.
Took one look at that guy.
and he caught a grabber.
And Corrigan?
Left with two bullets in him.
But I gotta tell ya...
I can understand
why Vinny croaked like that.
That Corrigan guy...
He didn't seem human.
[man. over radio] Good evening. This is
Houseman Welch welcoming you
to a special Christmas edition
of the Hermes Theater.
Tonight. as I do every year
at this festive time.
your obedient servant will be reading
from Charles Dickens’ immortal tale
of redemption. A Christmas Carol.
But first. a word from our friends
at the Conway Soup Company.
[radio clicks off]
[dramatic music playing]
-[loud bang]
-[startled gasp]
-[bang]
[creaking]
Not tonight. Jacob Marley.
[bang]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
I've just about had it with you!
Please. Roger!
Please don't hurt me anymore. [groans]
-I'm just getting started.
-[snow crunches]
[suspenseful music playing]
[belabored] Roger... Marshall.
Corrigan?!
[grunting and panting]
[suspenseful music continues]
[panting]
[grunts]
[groans]
[panting]
[groaning and panting]
[dispatcher] Possible break-in
at Bergduff’s Department store.
34th and O’Neil.
Two men spotted in the area. and. uh.
witness claims one of 'em's a zombie.
-[tires screech]
-[suspenseful music playing]
[panting]
[shrieks. groans]
[groaning and panting]
He's gone.
[chuckling]
I'm safe. I'm safe. and he can't get in--
[gasps]
What do you want from me. Corrigan?
Vengeance.
You're here about Veronica?
Uh. listen... [sputters]
That wasn't on me! She was my wife!
She fell down those stairs! The jury said!
Come on. brother.
You're not gonna ice me
over one worthless piece--
[grunts. groans]
[growls]
[groaning and panting]
-[chuckles. laughs]
-[distant music]
-[engine revving]
-[shrieking]
-[bones crunching]
-[brakes slam]
[gasps and grunts]
-[engine revs]
-[tires screeching]
[dramatic music playing]
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
-[Gordon] It's Dad.
Looks like I'll be later than expected.
I swear Christmas Eve's
just like a full moon in this town.
All the loonies come out.
[Barbara] Should I wait up?
[Gordon] You don't have to sweetheart.
I'll see you in the morning.
-Are you okay? You sound...
-No. no. I'm fine.
It's just...
I can't get Corrigan out of my head.
The sound of him screaming.
his body writhing in pain. I...
Forget Corrigan.
He did what he did and paid for it.
[Gordon] You are here. Alive and well.
Justice.
That's my early Christmas present.
I left you some of my traditional eggnog
in the fridge.
Your eggnog is awful. Dad.
And that's part of the tradition.
[chuckles]
I'll see you soon.
[phone clatters]
[dramatic music playing]
[dispatcher] Looks like our zombie's
been spotted again.
Sixth and 51st near Wycliffe Center.
[Welch. over radio]
"Then he heard the noise much louder.
on the floors below.
then coming up the stairs.
then coming straight towards his door!
It came on through the heavy door..."
Geez. late again.
Considering what I pay that broad...
-You'd think she'd be a--
-[knocking]
-[on radio] "Who are you?"
-Get that.
[suspenseful music playing]
[on radio] "'Who were you then?'
said Scrooge. raising his voice."
[ominous music playing]
Freddy... Borke.
Corrigan? But... but word
from my boys is you're dead!
[grunts. struggling]
[neck cracks]
[grunts]
[groans]
[gasps. pants]
What do you want from me?
Vengeance.
[music intensifies]
[grunts. groans]
[panting]
[grunts and pants]
[whimpers]
[engine revs]
[tires screech]
-[pants and grunts]
-[suspenseful music continues]
Oh! No!
Not you too! [gasps]
[grunting]
[groans]
[rattling]
[high-pitched ringing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[panting]
[groans]
[high-pitched ringing]
[gasps]
[pants and grunts]
-[music intensifies]
-[struggling]
[screams]
[shrieks. whimpers
[snaps]
[screaming]
-[stabbing sound]
-[crowd screaming]
[dramatic music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[phone ringing]
Dad?
[Batman] Vinny DeLeon. Roger Marshall.
Freddy Borke.
Batman.
I need to know how they're connected
to Jim Corrigan.
-[Barbara] Corrigan? Corrigan's dead.
-I beg to differ.
He's alive?
-Peterson's experiment. It must've...
-What do these three men have in common?
DeLeon. he...
[Batman] Bilked dozens of people
out of their life savings.
Marshall murdered his wife.
Borke had his fingers
deep in the drug trade.
I know all that. What's the connection?
Corrigan was the arresting officer
in all three cases.
[Batman] And?
There wasn't sufficient
evidence to convict.
So it's unfinished business.
Hooking the fish that got away.
You got away too. Barbara.
What? No.
There's no reward anymore.
He has no earthly reason to--
We don't know what he's thinking.
Call your father. Get protection.
-If he is coming for you. then--
-[hangs up]
Then I'll be ready.
-[dramatic music playing]
-[people screaming]
[tires screeching]
[screaming continues]
[dramatic music continues]
Corrigan.
[fighting grunts and groans]
[heavy breathing]
[grunts and groans continue]
[exciting music playing]
[heavy breathing. groans]
[groans]
-[cracking]
-[pained grunts]
[groans]
[tracks squeaking]
[dramatic music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Time to end this.
One way or another.
[suspenseful music continues]
[belabored breathing]
[pants and groans]
[Corrigan groaning] Barbara...
Gordon.
Not another step.
Ready to die again? You son of a bitch.
Barbara.
I never hurt you!
I'm not some criminal who escaped justice!
You tried to kill me. For money!
So why. Jim? Why are you here?
What do you want from me?
[belabored] Forgiveness.
[pained panting]
[groaning. gasping]
[shivering] Please.
Forgive me.
[wind blowing]
[grunting]
Barbara!
[gasps. groans]
Dead.
He's dead.
He came all this way and...
He just wanted me to forgive him.
That's all.
[emotional music playing]
[distant sirens]
[brakes screeching]
You all right?
[sighs] Honestly?
No.
But... I think I will be.
[emotional music continues]
-[engine revs]
-[brakes screech]
[melancholy music playing]
[credits music playing]